Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Episode 119
Every soul will taste death, my dear.
As the apostles and prophets
pass into the eternal world...
we'll leave when the time is right.
How happy we offer our soul for the sake of truth
and write our name with the martyrs.
What we should do is to carry the banner they left us and pass it on from generation to generation.
Inshallah.
If there is a painful side to death...
It is the longing of the living
for those who are gone.
But the world is strange.
The home of alienation is a place
where we suffer from longing.
Our meeting is at home.
May Allah make it our share to meet
in the abode of survival.
Amin.
Amin, my Sheikh.
Bengi Hatun, don't be sad.
Don't think pessimistic.
We will avenge Öktem Bey
and everyone else.
I bellieve, you will not leave our
blood on the ground, however...
Will you avenge us by being under
the command of Nayman, Osman Bey?
If you want death to stop at Öktem...
You will obey my command, Osman.
If you do not enter into my command...
I will kill all your loved
ones in front of your eyes.
I give you time until tomorrow.
Make up your mind.
Either you come under my command...
Or you bury your loved ones
under the soil.
Who of my family are you going to
sacrifice this time to take your revenge?
Don't, Osman Bey.
Don't ever touch anyone in my family.
If you are going to sacrifice anyone,
let it be me, Osman Bey.
Bengi Hatun.
Your words are sharper than a dagger.
I know, I know you're hurt.
But we will be relatives soon.
Never forget this.
Öktem Bey offered
his head for the calling.
And tomorrow it will be Osman Bey.
Our calling is greater than everything.
I know for sure.
You are in pain and the pain
is gnawing at your heart.
However...
Never forget how great our calling is.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My sheikh.
Nayman has gone to Söğüt.
And he met Mother Sultan.
He must have gone to hold her accountable.
But we cannot know on which
side Mother Sultan will stand.
We will take our precautions...
to understand the situation.
Who will we trust, Osman Bey?
How do we know that İsmihan Sultan
will not sell us out?
Nayman will extend his hand to
her and ask for her friendship.
Who will we trust, Osman Bey?
The man who killed my husband is extending
one hand to us and the other to İsmihan.
Who will we trust?
It's okay to hold the hand that
reaches out to us for help.
We respect it.
But if that hand is
extended to break us..
We will not leave bones in it, Inshallah.
They both reached out to break.
We will not forget this.
We will not leave him unpunished.
Nayman fights with his army.
İsmihan fights with her tricks.
If united...
It will be difficult for us.
Let's stop Nayman first.
And then it will be the
turn of Mother Sultan.
But it's still too early for that.
Söğüt
You pretended to be loyal
to me and united with Osman.
I did what's necessary.
Is it necessary to betray me, woman?
Do you not want to be
accepted into this land?
Olof killed many people here.
His life would have hurt you, Nayman.
If someone dies, I decide that.
And if anyone survives, I decide that.
Neither you nor Osman.
Until Osman is by my side,
you will never be with him again.
Do you think Osman will
come under your command?
I don't think, İsmihan
I know this.
What is your goal, Nayman?
My goal...
is so big that neither
you nor Osman can understand it.
Whatever your goal is...
I know Osman bey very well.
He isn't good at trading
He offers his head, but does not
come under your command.
This is a mistake.
Osman will come
under my command.
And it will happen thanks to you.
If I can help you, that's
great, Commander Nayman.
But I don't think so.
I am always beside you.
And ready to do whatever it takes, Nayman.
What does it take for Osman?
What you said a while ago was true.
Osman is a bad trader.
He gives his soul and does
not take orders from anyone.
Even you couldn't stop him.
But he will come to protect his people.
I'm always with you, Nayman.
I'm ready to do what it takes.
I don't think you
understand, Mother Sultan.
Soldier.
Send a messenger to Konya.
Tell them, if Mother Sultan disobeys me...
the head of her son Aladdin will be hung
at the entrance to Konya.
And now you understand, Mother Sultan.
All of you are at my command.
And all your souls rest upon my sword.
Mother Sultan will
calm Nayman and calm the atmosphere.
And he will think that his
campaign has succeeded.
And then I will put my sword on
the neck of Mother Sultan.
Why would Nayman stop?
Why would they tolerate us when
the opportunity was in his hand?
Do you see that he has taken it easy on us
after all, Turgut Bey?
- Don't you consider losing my husband a loss?
- Bengi Hatun, stop.
Your pain is our pain, and
our pain is great.
My question is different from that.
I'm talking about Nayman, who can attack our lands, what will make him stop now?
We understood that he
would not attack us...
but what does it mean that he wants you
under his command, Osman Bey?
I don't know why he did this.
I thought he did it
to win his army a crushing victory.
But he silenced all the Beys
and separated us.
He must have another goal.
He must have a greater purpose than that.
How will we know this goal?
Did you keep the prisoners?
We captured the three Mongol soldiers that
Nayman gave to Olof and set the rest free.
We'll interrogate
the prisoners first to find out.
Meanwhile, distribute the
Beys' share of the gold.
- Let's do what we have to do.
- Your command, my Bey.
You bear this burden, but there are
other heavy burdens, Osman Bey.
We ask Allah not to burden us with
what we can't carry. Do not worry at all.
We will definitely get through that.
If you excue me, my Sheikh.
Let each of you go to your job.
My Bey, what is your purpose
from these prisoners?
We'll wreak havoc with
them in the Nyman army.
Shall we do it with two
or three soldiers, my Bey?
We will destroy Nayman's campaign.
Tell me, do you know the
story of David and Goliath?
David was weaker than Goliath.
But he knew all his weaknesses.
And these captives will be so for us.
They will be the first stone
that David will throw at Goliath.
We will scatter Nayman's army completely.
Osman Bey is coming!
You're the remnants of swords that
do not know for whom you are fighting.
You are right, Osman.
It doesn't matter who I'm fighting for...
but the important thing is that I
hold my sword against you.
Nayman used you against Olof.
While you had many dreams...
and the battles you would have fought...
We still have these dreams.
Kill me that God embraces me.
Our goal is to erase people like you.
And this will be your end, whether
we die or live.
Tell me who we are.
You are the Muslims
We will drain your offspring and
destroy your sanctities.
We rebelled against our own for that
and turned our backs on Ghazan Khan.
We will erase you, Osman.
Your Allah, whom
you trust, will not benefit you.
It's time to tell you the bad news.
So know the truth about the man you are under.
Commander Nayman was honored by the
grace of Islam on these Muslim lands...
that he came to sweep with his armies.
Is it true what you say, Osman Bey?
He says your case is over.
We've watched the roads as
you have commanded...
and Nayman's caravan will
come to our lands tomorrow.
They came from the way
you told us, Osman Bey.
This is the second stone that
we will throw in the face of Goliath.
We'll throw it at the right time so that
it will benefit our campaign more.
Your campaign, Osman Bey.
My Bey, they asked me to
deliver this letter to you.
From whom is this letter?
For those who carry their secrets with
their hearts and not with their minds.
- I'll go to them.
- Okay.
Öktem tribe
Bengi Hatun is coming!
The chair is empty, Bengi Hatun.
We have to hold a council to choose a Bey,
as Öktem Bey has no son.
The chair must find someone to occupy it.
Tell me which chair was left
empty, so our chair remained empty?
What is the urgency? Yesterday, I buried
my husband's body in the dirt.
But I see that your voices
are rising in this regard.
You are crying over the empty chair today.
But if I order you tomorrow and...
tell you that we will stand against Nayman
who killed my husband and our children...
What will be the situation?
Will your voices rise then?
It won't.
Your voices only get louder in my tent.
Your Bey was martyred without
blinking an eyelid out of fear of death.
But what about you?
Can you be brave like him?
Raise your voice now, come on.
Nayman is the commander of a large army,
and you know the number of our warriors.
What can we do against him?
You will then let the blood of your Bey
and your children be in vain, will you not?
You can't do anything
with your cowardice.
- Osman Bey will punish Nayman.
- He will certainly punish him.
But Osman often goes on and on.
Those who have been killed is
from our tribe.
And I will not waste time with the
politics that Osman follows.
But I see at the same time that
this will not happen to you.
When I say Nayman, your hearts tremble.
That is why
none of you have the right to this chair.
A hero who doesn't accept that Öktem Bey's
blood should be in vain must sit in this chair.
And until he
comes, I'll sit on this chair.
It's up to you, Bengi Hatun,
but who is this hero you speak of?
- Can I come in?
- Come in.
Bengi Hatun, Bala Hatun and
her attendants are here.
Go ahead.
Now you get out, come on.
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Well, Bengi Hatun...
Why are Beys here?
And what will it be, Bala Hatun?
They ask what we will do
after losing Öktem Bey.
Is this reasonable at a time like this?
We have recently buried Öktem Bey.
They see it right, Ayşe Hatun.
So that the chair
does not remain empty.
It's good that you came, for
I was coming to you.
- Please be seated.
- No, thank you.
We have come to say our
condolences.
Well, what were
you going to tell us?
The matter of Aktemur and Alçiçek has
been around for a long time.
I say let's tie the knot right away.
Mother!
Do you hear what you're saying?
My father is dead.
Alçiçek is right, this isn't appropriate until
40 days have passed since Öktem Bey's death.
Öktem is a martyr.
He does not want us to mourn him.
This issue has dragged on for a long time.
We have to shut people's mouths.
Bengi Hatun.
I don't think Aktemur
would agree to that.
Listen to me and
let's wait a little longer.
- At least...
- I said what I said.
Either the wedding will
take place on the spot...
or we
cancel the engagement.
- It's up to you.
- Bengi Hatun.
Why this hurry? There is a
funeral at your house.
Is there something
we don't know?
Tell me, what is Nayman's main
campaign?
The conversion of Ghazan Mahmud Khan
has caused much confusion.
Among his commanders and
even among the Mongol forces.
Sülemiş rebelled because
he was not given the sovereignty of Anatolia.
Nayman and his brother Talay
want to expand that rebellion.
Good.
Everyone will live
as they deserve.
Let them mess with each other.
But their main goal
is to create a state.
Talay gathers the army in
the Mamluk state.
And Nayman is
getting stronger here.
That is why Nayman did not want
to use all his power against us.
Their campaign is fueled
by the enemies of Islam.
But the alliance that they are preparing for
will inflict injustice on Islamic lands only.
Don't ever worry.
I will prevent it as long as I breathe.
That's why your state lives.
You have the strength, courage
and ability, Osman Bey.
Only you can stop them.
Thank you.
It is from the caliph.
Talk.
What is happening in Konya?
Konya is in our hands, Commander Nayman.
The existence of Sultan
Aladdin is a formality.
İsmihan Sultan is the real danger.
She dreams of reviving a dead country.
İsmihan.
Mother Sultan.
Dozens of foxes roam around her head.
But I will tie all the fox tails together.
And if she makes a mistake...
her son Aladdin will die.
I will destroy her and destroy Osman!
What's going on in your
head, Commander Nayman?
You'll hear about it, it's coming.
The issue is more important
than we expected.
Even the caliph sent us
news of the matter.
Well, is the issue clear
in Muslim countries?
The issue is clear, however...
they ignore it, Osman Bey.
Ghazan Khan's choice of true religion
does not erase the past.
They support Talay, who attacked the
Turkish Beys in the Mamluk state.
Osman Bey.
Some of us have fallen into the
trap of resentment and hatred.
And the rest are
in heedlessness.
And many of us are immersed
in our own interests.
The situation is very serious.
Yes.
There are still people who
stand up for what is right.
And there are still those who
did not fall into oblivion.
There are still those who seek
to spread the system around the world.
What are you going to do, Osman Bey?
Will you accept Commander Nayman's offer?
Will you submit to him?
Did you not know that I would accept
this job from the start?
Courage is enough to fight the enemy.
Understanding what is going on in the head of the enemy requires great intelligence, Osman Bey.
What you say is true.
Thank Allah we have both.
May your war be blessed, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
- May you be safe.
Ask forgiveness of Allah and repent to Him.
What is this?
What did your mothers breastfeed you
when you were babies?
Vizier Savelli.
You came.
That's why you survived, merchant.
If you submit to me...
Your entire clan will
survive, not just you.
You will trade all over
the world and not just in this country.
Thank Allah.
I'm basically the biggest
dealer in this country.
Merchant Bayındır is a
good choice, Captain Nayman.
He has a great share in what
Osman made us live in Konya.
I know that.
I know all of this.
And now...
Merchant, you'll turn your back on Osman
and Mother Sultan too.
We have a calling.
Not for a few chests of gold.
Not a few boxes of gold.
And you soul too.
Vizier Savelli.
You set your side from the start,
right?
I'm a smart man, Bayındır.
I recommend this to you too.
The gold that Osman stole from me.
You'll learn all about it first, merchant.
Then, you will tell me every step
Mother Sultan takes and...
everything that goes on between her and Osman.
This is the key that will open
all doors for you, merchant.
Oh my.
Where are you?
Is there no one?
Murat.
Baysungur.
Where are you?
Is there no one?
Ülgen Hatun.
Where is everybody?
They're at war, Cerkutay.
Have you forgotten?
Did we take İnegöl?
Yes, we took it.
Thanks to Gürbüz Alp.
Who?
Is it thanks to Gurbuz Alp?
You opened the door
and I protected you.
What did Gürbüz do?
What did Gürbüz do that we should take
credit for taking the castle to him?
I gave my soul, my soul.
What did Gürbüz do?
Or are you jealous of Gürbüz Alp?
Why would I be jealous of Gürbüz?
What am I going to be jealous of?
Yes.
You are jealous, of course.
Gürbüz Alp is very hardworking
and very talented.
He is very brave and strong.
And he eats more food than you.
Since then...
since then...
If Gürbüz Alp does not enter,
you cannot enter the kitchen.
Also, why are you interfering with me?
Don't turn your back on me, Ülgen.
Ülgen.
I.. you.. you..
Cerkutay, did he wake up?
Thank Allah, you woke up!
Praise be to Allah!
He woke up!
He woke up from a very deep dream!
Isn't that right, Cerkutay?
Drink, Cerkutay, drink.
Drink
May your wounds be healed.
Gürbüz.
Get out in front of me.
I'm going to go and tell
Kumral Abdal this good news.
Why are you crying?
I was so afraid, Cerkutay.
I mean, you scared us a lot.
Not only me,
but everyone cried for you.
Especially Boran Alp,
he cried more than me.
You...
Aren't you a brave girl?
I think you aren't afraid.
I am not afraid.
I am not afraid, however...
I am not afraid of the infidels.
I was afraid you might get sick.
Everybody's afraid of this.
Anyway.
I'll bring you soup.
I'll prepare it.
Ülgen.
I got scared too.
I was afraid you wouldn't be able to
get out of that castle alive.
But you got out safe.
I offended you greatly.
My brother's life is safe.
Punish me.
I accept everything you say.
Since you said this, you know
what your actions caused.
Isn't that right, Esma?
I know.
I am ashamed to ask for forgiveness.
There is no pardon for what I have done,
I accept any punishment you decide.
If only I hadn't known that you made
this mistake for your brother's life...
I would have killed you the day I
learned of your betrayal.
You're right, Malhun Hatun.
And now you will promise me.
You will never make such a mistake again.
I won't.
I will never do this again.
I learned my lesson.
I did so many bad things.
Punish me.
Punish me now so that it does
not remain for the hereafter.
I forgive you for my right, Esma.
You are not going anywhere.
You will pay for what you did
by living here with us.
I promise, Malhun Hatun.
I promise you.
I will protect your children
even if it costs me my life.
I will get you right one day.
Tell me, how are the preparations?
The preparations are
complete, Osman Bey.
We are ready, very ready.
So say quick, we don't
have much time.
You go alone to
the hole of the foxes we want to kill.
Don't.
All the holes in this country are ours.
The uninvited guest is Nayman.
Either he will die or he will be gone.
We are not going to give up.
We go to receive and take.
Inshallah.
- Inshallah, my Bey.
- Inshallah.
Nevertheless, take care of
yourself.
At the slightest mistake, the place of the
hunter and the prey change, Osman Bey.
What do we do next?
So, we won't make ay mistake.
We won't.
It's time.
Release the captives.
Your command, my Bey.
Turgut.
In my absence, the estates and warriors
who are at my command...
will be your lead.
Your words will echo on my sword.
We'll be where
you said it at the time you said it.
Everything will go as
we would like, Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Give me your blessings.
- We give you blessings, my Bey.
We give you blessings, my Bey.
Give us your blessings, my Bey.
I give you blessings.
Take care of yourself.
We still have a lot of
work to do.
Let's get over this first.
We'll get thorugh this.
We'll look at the rest.
Hear me now well.
The merchant will bring what we ask.
And you shall become a
viper in this region, Savelli.
Your command, Commander Nayman.
İsmihan will think that you
are on her side.
You will complete what the merchant lacks.
We'll make a big fire.
You will burn the enemy
and we'll warm our people.
Go get wood for that fire.
Let's go.
You will target the convoy first.
This will be your first campaign.
You'll get news after I say it.
I'll tell Nayman that there is a spark of
disobedience within the army...
and it will flare up.
Then the soldiers will enter, who
will say that Nayman has chosen Islam.
You will release them.
My Bey.
Aren't these the Muslim army
of Ghazan Khan?
Why do they oppose our religion?
No.
These are the opponents of Ghazan Khan.
They are the ones who want to erase
Islam from these lands.
When they hear that
Nayman has chosen Islam...
They will think he has been deceived.
And the disobedience will begin.
Then?
When it appears that
what I've said is true...
Nayman will trust me completely.
He'll think I'm defending him.
And then, the main topic...
He will tell me which country campaigns
he would like to establish one by one...
Those who want to know
the truth will walk to the fire.
And the secret of the fire
is for those who enter the fire only.
Thank you.
Let's see if Osman
and İsmihan will burn or warm.
Gök Talay.
Let the soldiers go out
and welcome the oncoming caravan.
Great Commander Nayman.
Come here.
Osman Bey is coming.
Let him come.
You will die Osman, you will die.
- You will die, Osman.
You will die.
- You will die.
- you will die.
You will die Osman, you will die.
Is that
possible, mother?
We buried Öktem Bey yesterday.
What will people say?
Son, we said, we said that too.
However, she doesn't listen.
She says, if you don't
have a wedding...
she will break the engagement.
What does thisHatun want to do?
What are you seeking again?
Something comes
to my mind, however...
Are you thinking what I'm thinking, Bala?
What do you think
Bengi Hatun thinks?
Öktem Bey doesn't have a son, does he?
Bengi Hatun sat on the throne today, but
Beys will not remain silent about this situation.
- She would like...
- Mother.
Sons.
Let your path be open.
Thank you.
Take care of each other.
Be careful, okay?
Let's go.
Let's distribute the gold that the people
deserve and lighten the burden on our backs.
Let's go.
Warriors, warriors, come on to the horses.
Did Osman say his decision
so that we hasten to his sword?
Osman will say his decision.
Then we will know if his
sword is at our service.
Or is our sword on his neck?
My sword...
services my Allah only.
My Allah says to me, protect
your people.
The way to protect my people...
passes through you.
But...
Don't think I'm afraid
because your sword is on my neck.
If you would have been afraid, I would not
have wanted you in my army, Osman.
You are a brave man who
thinks of his people.
This is the thing that
keeps you alive.
Don't forget, cowards die every day.
And the brave die once.
But I would like all my soldiers
to hear your loyalty
So that
no one shall be disrespectful again.
Say Osman.
I
The Bey of Kayis.
The owner of all the properties
in the border areas, Osman Bey.
My sword...
...is at the service of commander Nayman.
My life depends on his words
and my moves are with his commands.
Even I hardly heard you.
Repeat Osman!
From now on...
My sword...
...is at the service of commander Nayman!
Keep it.
Do you know why I did not kill you and
wanted you to be under my command, Osman?
Say.
Because you have no equal.
Otherwise, I would have killed
you on the first day.
Let's go into the tent.
I have a lot to ask
They are coming
Prepare your fishook, Boran
We'll fish today.
Be vigilant.
The goods and weapons in this upcoming
caravan are very important to Nayman.
If we manage take them,
we will severely break their power.
The more we sieze his ammunation,
the greater we hit him.
I hope so, Turgut Bey, I hope so.
Now!
Oh right!
Table!
Osman!
This lamb was bred in a special way.
Only the toughest warriors deserve it.
Thank you, thank you.
You're so honored, Nayman.
Help yourself
Don't worry
I made the Muslim butchers slaughter it.
Thank you.
In the name of Allah,
the most gracious, the most merciful
Well, tell me.
Is me being a Muslim a problem for you?
An obedient Muslim is not a problem for me
Well, what about Ghazan Khan?
A Muslim is the ruler of the state.
Is that a problem for you?
Whoever is under
my command can be a Muslim.
But he who is in a higher position than me,
can never.
Ghazan Khan made a choice,
and he will pay for it
And what about you?
You are serving a non-Muslim person.
Will this bother you?
My only goal is the people of my tribe.
I serve whomever I ought to serve
for their sake..
Well, you say.
What is your purpose?
What will you do with Ghazan Khan?
It is enough for us to part ways now.
I will draw my own path.
I see that road will lead to a state.
I will found a state, Osman
A state, huh?
State issue is a huge issue.
So...
How will you do that?
Strength lies in weapons and gold.
There are caravans coming to me right now.
Caravans that carry weapon and gold to me.
They will make me stronger here.
And I will create a state with that power.
Well, will we have our share of the gold?
You just need to be loyal to me, Osman.
Just serve to me and both glory
and gold shall be yours.
Eyvallah, Eyvallah.
(Thank you)
So, as a first service to you...
Let me warn you.
Those tribes won't listen to you.
And they will attack your caravan.
This is how it happens here.
Not safe at all.
They will attack the caravan.
No one can dare to do that, Osman.
Eyvallah (okay).
Whatever you think.
Now Nayman has taken the major hit.
Good for you alps.
The prey we caught turned out to be
bigger than we expected
What is it, Turgut Bey?
This is the map of the route of caravans.
It marks the places where Nayman's
caravans are waiting.
We are going to find them so easily.
We will destroy them all.
Oi Masha Allah!
Tell me, Turgut Bey.
We asked for an eye, Lord gave us two.
Such an unfortuneate, Kutan!
Turgut Bey.
Let's knit a dress for Nayman
out of this silk.
Alright, Boran.
You are in your merciful day.
...but, my Bey...
Isn't silk forbidden for men?
Forbidden for men,
not for that dishonorable Nayman.
Nayman must be regretting
about how wrong he was!
Eyvallah!
Osman Bey's game has succeeded
But this is still just the beginning.
We're not even halfway there.
We will distribute the goods
to the people now.
Come on, let's go
Sogut.
You're late, Bayindir.
Where have you been?
Forgive me, Mother Sultan.
You are right
...but you know, I've been away from
commerce for a long time
I said let's go out and
check out my stores.
Future is uncertain.
We don't know when
it might occur to Osman Bey...
...and he decides to
shut down my stores!
Can't he do that?
Maybe.
He wouldn't, Bayindir.
Osman Bey and I
are in the same side now
The more you earn he will earn too.
You know what's best.
You have a point in the present time,
Mother Sultan.
But only Allah alone can know the future.
Until yesterday, you and Osman Bey
were staunch enemies
However, today...
Like I said, you know what's best.
If you say we are friends, we are.
If I say we are enemies,
I will sharpen my sword for them.
Nayman won't stop after cutting
Oktem Bey's head, Bayindir.
If we side with Nayman...
We will lose all the Turkmen tribes.
If we side with Osman Bey's side...
We'll both be good with Turkmens and...
We'll have a chance to get rid of Nayman.
Dear Mother Sultan, who is Osman Bey?
Who is he to unite with us
and remove Nayman?
Still, you know the best.
I am thinking about the gold.
The gold that Osman Bey took from
the rest of the Beys.
The gold has not been found yet.
Osman Bey must have a plan.
Forget about the gold now.
Go to our people and fulfill their needs
in the name of Mother Sultan.
As you order, Mother Sultan.
Bayindir's mind is clouded, Celali.
I don't trust him.
Tell me about every step he takes.
As you command, Mother Sultan.
Mother Sultan.
My Bey!
She was going to kill me!
She was about to kill me!
Why?
Because I cooperated with Osman Bey!
What has changed now?
Who am I?
She is telling me to side with Osman Bey!
Her face doesn't even go red!
You are right, my Bey.
Yet I have an important news.
Say.
Aktemur and Hatuns
departed to hand out the gold.
Yes, just like that.
Osman Bey is the sign of justice.
He will definitely share the gold.
Good, good.
We'll go after the gold at once!
We act according to our interests, Huseyin.
We'll work for ourselves.
We will work for ourselves.
Only for ourselves.
Let's go Huseyin.
Commander Neyman
The caravan has been attacked.
How did you see it coming, Osman?
This land is my home, Nayman.
I told you.
I'm the one who knows the best here.
You can think like this:
A caravan of yours was attacked.
But you gained a commander who saw in advance
that the caravan would be attacked.
If you cooperate with me...
You will earn ten times as much.
You are right.
A caravan goes, a caravan comes.
But I now have Osman!
Exactly.
We were talking about the state
before the caravan issue.
Tell me now.
You talk about gold and weapon.
But you need to be men for these.
You need number.
What's your plan here?
You understand the affairs of this country,
don't you, Osman?
We thought about this and
performed our campaign.
I'll collect Muslim children from the tribes.
They will be raised for me.
They will serve me.
Doesn't that bother you?
As long as you don't touch my tribe,
it's not a problem for me.
I said this before too.
Whoever does not side with me is against me.
From now on, everyone will walk alone.
Osman.
Osman, Osman.
We will do very big business together.
History will talk about us forever!
Will you found this country alone?
I have you!
Eyvallah, (thank you)you consider
us on your way. That makes me happy.
But I am not talking about that.
Do you have a brother behind you?
Or a friend? I'm talking about this.
Are you trying to imply something?
Since we will walk together...
Since I will protect you...
I want to know if
there's someone who supports you.
You ask a lot of questions, Osman.
That's enough for you now.
Alright then,
let's get over with the questions.
I have another warning for you.
According to the news I received.
There is a preparation to rebel against you
in the army.
What is your tongue saying, Osman?!
The truth!
The truth.
You still don't know my army yet.
You will get to know now.
Let the Majors come.
This road takes us to their hole, brother.
You're right, Aykurt.
Since they're rushing to Nayman...
This means that they suspected something.
They must have.
This suspicion will cause discord
in Nayman's army.
Come on, there's nothing,
let's get back to the headquarters.
Nayman will answer to the soldiers.
He betrayed Tengri
(Turkish-Mongolian God)
Osman Bey's plan is going well, Aykurt
Let's go.
Alps!
Who are you_
Are you from the Kayi tribe?
We are from the family of Osman Bey.
Say, what is the reason you hurry?
The Mongol soldiers collect children from the
Turkmen tribes in order to raise them.
They entered the nearby tribes.
What are you saying?
Where are they now?
Wesent several alps behind their caravan.
Part of them went to neighboring tribes.
But their number is very large.
We can do nothing alone.
We need help.
Aktemur.
You deliver the gold,
we go after those dogs.
Let the alps go with you.
We will take care of ourselves.
Not possible.
Gold is important.
It should be distributed to the people
without any problems.
We will take care of ourselves.
Son!
When your work is done, you will join us.
Come on.
Eyvallah (Okay)
- Let's go!
Alps!
Let'S go.
What shall we do now, my Bey?
They are splitting.
Don't you know, Huseyin.
Our only goal is gold.
We can get by for the rest of our lives with it.
We'll go after Aktemur.
Your command, my Bey.
Also, I have an account with Aktemur that
I haven't settled yet.
When he dies while sharing the gold,
nobody will suspect me.
Let's go.
We hit the caravan and not only hit it,
we struck fear into Nayman's heart as well.
Osman Bey told us to attack the caravan
and we did it. Mission accomplished, Turgut Bey.
Yes, we have been successful, thank Allah.
What do we do next, Turgut Bey?
Those valiants will tell us what's next.
Peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you too.
Tell me.
We did what you told us, Turgut Bey,
we released the two Mongol soldiers at Inegol.
Eyvallah (thank you)
Well, do you think they were convinced
that Nayman had the honor of converting to Islam?
They will forget their horses, but they will never
forget what Nayman did, Turgut Bey.
Were they angry?
Their fear outweighted their anger...
but after they enter the army headquarters,
their anger will outweight their fear.
Then the rebellion will break out
in the army headquarters, huh?
Osman Bey managed the toughest challange.
Thank Allah.
Majors! Osman says there are
rebellious voices within my army.
Each and every Mongol soldiers
are loyal to Nayman.
This army was made up of believers only,
there are no cracks in the army, Nayman.
You claim that your Majors control
every single Mongol soldier in their troop.
You claim that they know each one of them
and control each one of them, is that true?
Do you doubt their loyalty?
Then tell me.
If Ghazan Khan sent you a letter...
...and told you to leave the army,
what would you do?
Our devotion is only to Nayman!
Here you are, seeing
with your own eyes, Osman.
What I see is the loyalty of the leaders only.
But what about the soldiers below?
A nail can save a horseshoe.
A horseshoe can save a horse.
A horse might save a man, and a man might
lead the entire army to victory or lead it to rebellion
I am still behind my words.
There are rebellion voices in your army.
It's hard to convince you, isn't it?
The same situation exists for you.
It is clear that you will not understand
without seeing and hearing.
Okay then.
Get out there, Nayman, you will answer!
Get out of your tent Nayman!
You have to answer us!
Answer us!
Get out, Nayman, get out!
A commander always listens to his soldiers.
That's the way since The Great Genghis.
Tell me, what is your problem?
Speak or you will die without
me knowing what your problem is!
Why did we come here, Nayman?
Let him talk.
Say.
Ghazan Khan lost his way, and we're behind
you, because you know the way, Nayman
Are you kidding us, Nayman?
Have you united with our enemy, Nayman?
What are you saying?
They say you converted to Islam, Nayman.
The whole army is talking about it
It is true that I united with Muslims.
It is true that I work with a Muslim ruler.
But I am not a Muslim!
Kagan!
Start the rituel!
Sky Tengri!
(Turkish-Mongolian God)
The three soldiers
who spoke will be forgiven.
And the other cowards who did not speak,
those who were scared will be hanged!
As Mighty Commander Nayman commands.
Forgive us, Nayman, forgive us
How did you know about the rebellion?
Do you have spies inside the army?
I am also a part of this army.
I knew this information in advance.
When you came to my tent and met Edebali...
Especially after you recovered my son Orhan,
this rumor was around.
It was clear that this would come up one day.
And I warned you.
Trust is not easily earned.
But it can be easily lost.
Come to the tent.
Now, Hatuns!
Let's go!
Do not leave those who touched childrne alive!
May the hands that extend
to our children be broken!
Children, oh, thank Allah!
Children, thank Allah you survived
Easy, easy, get up.
Come, come, come.
Come here.
Malhun.
Oh thank Allah!
- Are you okay?
- Are you fine?
Alright.
Come and rest now.
You are fine, right?
Malhun.
Come on, thank Allah.
Hey, let's get together.
- Come on, get up, kids
- Mashallah
Tell me, where are the rest of the kids?
I am talking to you!
Talk or I will cut off your head!
We need to find out
where the rest of the children are
Bala Hatun.
Let me find our alps
who pursued them and tell you
Do you know Enulok Cave?
Come over there when you learn.
We'll be there.
What do they want from our children?
They want our children
to rise their swords in our faces.
We cannot allow this.
Of course we will not allow.
Ayse, send word to Aktemur.
They're too many, we're going to need help.
We will send another word.
To whom?
To someone who can help us.
We distributed a portion of the gold, my Bey.
Good, let us lighten our burden.
My Bey.
Will we go to battle when
we're done with the gold?
We will go, Inshallah Kotlu, we will go.
Besides, Hatuns were sorry that Osman Bey
was fighting a hard fight there...
...and the only thing they needed to do
was to share the gold.
Now everyone needs to kill Mongol soldiers!
Let's go.
Come on, come on!
Tell me, what's going on?
They go to distribute
the rest of the gold, my Bey?
Why did they split up with the Hatuns?
Is there news about Osman Bey?
The Hatuns of Kayi tribe
are following the Mongol soldiers.
Also, they said something about Osman Bey.
What are they saying?
Osman Bey is playing
a game on Commander Nayman
You say it at the end
while you need to say it firstly!
Take, you gave me
what is more precious than gold.
We will be back quickly
My Bey, what about the gold?
We have something
more precious than gold, come on!
Nayman's headquarters
Today you did your tasks fully.
I am lucky to have a commander like you.
You put your sword at my command.
And I will give you this sword.
Whose sword is this?
This sword is the sword of a noble Turk
who served Gengish Khan.
It's Noyan's sword.
Noyan huh?
And you will serve me likewise.
And you will reward me like Genghis Khan, huh?
Prepare very well.
I grant you the control of
my army with this sword.
Now that you give me control...
So, I want to know.
Who is your friend and who is your enemy?
Aren't you afraid of Ghazan Khan's campaigns?
I wouldn't be afraid even if I was alone.
But I am not alone.
I have a brother, Talay
He strives with me for the same
end in the lands of the Mamluks
Gathering the army, gathering supporters.
He draws both Turk and Mongol Beys
to our side.
That is, you are the man here
and he is the man there.
Ghazan Khan is in trouble then.
Of course, but is he the only one?
Anyone who dares to stand up to us
is in trouble.
We'll be the trouble, Osman!
But there is a deficiency in your campaign.
I want to say that.
What is it? Say.
Everything you say today turns out true.
You are talking about a state.
Soldiers are needed for the state,
you have a lot of them.
When swords are needed...
Your caravans bring you swords
And if you want gold,
it is also on the way.
What is the shortage?
The missing thing is a characteristic
that will give you legitimacy.
You are not from a noble family.
No sword, no seal, no banner
left over from Genghis Khan.
Otherwise, otherwise
why should they stand behind you?
You are more than I expected.
I also have them, Osman.
The hugest.
There is a seal so big that it shakes the whole world,
not just the Mongols, and makes them line up behind me
The seal of Gengish Khan.
That seal is in our hands.
My brother Talay has it.
Every letter I write with that seal
will be considered an order.
All Mongol lords and kings
shall gather under my banner.
There was only one thing missing
in the state that I will found.
And it is not the seal.
And it was skillfull commanders, Osman.
As long as your sword is with me,
no one will stand against us...
Everyone, everyone will kneel before us.
The knee that does not kneel will be broken!
And the head that does not bow will be cut off!
My sword is at your command, never worry.
I'm going to get very big and make you big, Osman.
Eyvallah.
So, if you'll excuse me now, I'd like to rest.
Of course, Commander Osman, of course.
Oktem's Tents.
My condolences, Bengi Hatun.
Your pain is fresh, I know.
But know that from now on
I will always be by your side.
When you're in trouble, you'll find me first.
May Allah bless you, Mother Sultan.
But I no longer need anyone.
What do you mean by that, Bengi Hatun?
Aren't we together like we were?
Actually we need each other now.
My husband is gone, Mother Sultan.
My husband died because of that dog.
We are all very sad about this.
Oktem Bey was a valiant Bey.
We will definitely avenge him.
Have no doubt about it.
You will definitely get revenge.
But we can't undo
what happened to my family.
The dog, Olof, died.
And my husband is gone before I rejoice
in the revenge of my brother and my alps.
I no longer trust anyone.
Let your pain go away.
- And then we talk
- This pain does not go away, Mother Sultan.
If Nayman's head is cut off someday...
Then maybe my pain will ease.
But it does not go away.
This pain will remain with me until
I surrender my soul to the Creator
I promise we'll decapitate Nayman together
But first we must increase our strength, Bengi Hatun.
Who will sit on the throne?
My son Aktemur will sit on the throne.
Yenisehir
So Cerkutay, what are you thinking about?
Drink your soup and don't let it get cold!
I'm not hungry.
If you don't drink it, you can't get up.
Come on.
I'm not going to drink it,
Ulgen Hatun, I'm not!
Then don't!
You broke Ulgen's heart.
But your heart
hurts the most, doesn't it, Cerkutay?
Kumral Abdal.
What are you runnung away from, Cerkutay?
From the exam, you know, Kumral Abdal.
You know what's going on.
I'm afraid.
I am afraid of taking the exam again.
You can't run away from your fears, Cerkutay.
Especially from an exam, y
ou can never run away from it
What should I do?
You'll do what you always do, Cerkutay.
You will listen to your heart.
Death is certain.
You live what Allah has written for you.
You can't escape life either, Cerkutay.
You'll heal the broken hearts.
Life is short.
Life is too short to break a heart.
Eyvallah
(thank you)
So they are in Tasdelen.
That place is not suitable for battle.
How many are they?
I counted 50 people.
There are around 10 children.
When they find out that the soldiers
we slaughtered don't come...
...they will understand that
there is a problem.
For that reason,
we will attack them at the crack of dawn.
Malhun.
We have sent alps to the mansion.
We are just 15 people.
Will we be able to beat them in your opinion?
Of course.
Osman Bey risks his life in front of his enemies
I hope we will succeed in this.
Aktemur, any news from Osman Bey?
Is there anything else you want, Osman Bey?
No, thank you.
The seal of Gengish Khan.
That seal is in our hands.
Take it to my brother Talay.
Every letter I write with
that seal will count as an order
And all the Mongol leaders
and their kingdoms will gather under my banner
You will drown in your dreams.
Without that seal...
The country you will create
will become your tomb.
It will become your grave.
And the state I'll found will rise.
Nayman's Headquarters.
Osman is here.
He will pay for his actions.
Stop, let's see why he is here first.
Why do you look like a deadhead?
Come on.
Come to me.
Get away!
Commander Neyman!
Commander Neyman, I have news!
Where is my gold?
I don't see it.
I have brought you something
more valuable than gold, Commander Nayman
What is it?
Osman Bey.
What's wrong with him?
He's cheating again.
He allied with you to get information.
He still wants you dead.
Osman.
You're curious as to
why I'm here, aren't you?
In order to put out the fire that is about to rage
Catch Osman!
Come on hurry up!
Osman, catch Osman. Find Osman.
Catch Osman!
- Come on
- Don't let him run away.
Catch Osman!
Osman escaped!
He escaped!
Where is Osman?
Osman!
Bring Osman to me!
Now you're done, Osman!
Osman is escaping!
He will take the seal!
He heard about my plans and Talay!
Talay builds an army there!
The seal must be mine!
I was going to command the Beys
with that seal!
Our armies were going to unite!
We were going to destroy our enemies!
Osman knows this!
He'll try to be me.
Goktalha, kill him!
Osman will never reach his goal.
Commander, what about you?
I promised them.
Now I will keep my promise.
Nayman's arrival changed the whole game.
No matter what happens, the palace
must stand still.
I strive only for this, Mother Sultan.
If Nayman hurts even
one person in this land...
And if you do not prevent the Sultan
from being harmed while you are the Vizier....
Then consider yourself dead, Saveli.
Both my life and death is for
the supreme Seljuk state, Mother Sultan.
We will find all the connections
Mongols have, and erase them.
Who is Nayman's spy in Konya?
And where is he?
First we will find him.
We are after him, Mother Sultan.
When I find him, I will kill him myself.
We are going beyond the Seljuk state.
Nayman will raise the banner of rebellion.
They will take over the throne of Ghazan Khan.
The peace started by Ilkhanate will end.
Their intention is to shed blood.
What is there beyond the Seljuq state, my Bey?
Talay, Nayman's brother, has the seal.
He established his army with
the strength he took from the Beys of Mamluk.
Nayman did the same thing.
Since his arrival,
he has got along with the Beys.
He wanted to make me his commander
and he wanted gold too.
Their intention is not this land.
- What is their aim then, my Bey?
- Tabriz!
They want to take over the throne of Ghazan Khan!
And they want to rule that land.
And when they get what they want..
We are the ones whose blood
will be shed the most, right, my Bey?
They need the seal to break us.
The seal is in Talay's hands now.
It's a seal from Genghis Khan's council.
If you have the seal,
everything you say becomes an order.
That's why we won't let Nayman take it.
We'll take it.
That's our only shot.
If we fail, they'll found a state whose
only aim is to erase Islam from these lands.
Since we are the swords of Islam...
Let's pierce the heart of enemies!
We will never allow them!
Eyvallah (Yes) my Bey!
Let's go!
- Come on, sisters!
- Come on Alps! Kill the ignoble!
- Allah is eternal!
- Allah is righteous!
Watch your backs!
Sisters, we won't stop until
we kill 5 of them, let's go!
Brother, why don't we practice?
Is it...
If I take my sword out of its scabbard,
you will fall to the ground, my brother.
Let it out then, brother,
I am not afraid of you.
Come on brother, you must be rusty.
You are out of your mind.
I will knock you down now.
- Allah is eternal.
- Allah is righteous.
Come on brother.
No, brother.
My hand does not obey me.
- You'll get better, brother, Also Kumral Ab...
- No!
No Aladdin.
Don't tell anyone that my hand is not working.
I will not bring pain into my family's heart
at this difficult time.
I won't tell them brother.
But you will not surrender
and you will not be defeated, my brother!
No backup on the way, Bala?
Hold on a little longer!
I am here, Hatuns!
You shameless soldiers!
I will burn anyone who touches children!
We won't stop until
we chop everyone's throats off!
Come on!
Obviously we are not alone!
Children!
It's over, my children, it's over.
Come to me, Come!
Thank Allah that all of you survived
Come on, come on, come on, come on
Praise be to Allah, go down slowly,
go down slowly, go down slowly
Let's go
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah, children, thank Allah.
Come on baby, come on.
Bring water!
You will all get back to your mothers.
You caught us just in time, Bengi Hatun.
You told us at the right time.
When I got the news, I felt so proud.
Since we are relatives now...
...we'll have each other's backs,
won't we, Bengi Hatun?
Come on, come on baby, come on.
Osman's son.
Tengri(God) healed you
But you lost your way.
Osman is coming.
The arrow has come out of the bow.
I want Osman.
Are you well prepared?
Yes sir.
Let's go.
Alps, it's a trap!
Sir, they're surrounding us.
Erlik Khan is our guide.
And war is our wedding!
Your head is our share, Osman!
Sir, these dogs are surrounding all over us.
We'll send horses at them
and surprise them!
And then we'll form the shield system!
Come on, be prepared!
Okay my Bey!
Come on! Now!
Take cover!
Sir, we are out of arrow.
Come to us, come to us.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com